

# KATE YANG GRAPHIC & UI DESIGNER

#### CONTACT

0936178048



etim816@gmail.com



https://etim816.github.io/portfolio/

#### **EDUCATION**

NTCUST 2006

Department of Multimedia Design

#### **SKILLS**

**UI** Design **UX** Design Prototyping Graphic Design



#### Software

Adobe Creative Suite Photoshop. Illustrator. Indesign Sketch | Flinto | HTML | CSS3 Power Point | Word

#### **PROFILE**

I'm with 8+ years of experience in graphic designer. Last work I joined Vehicle team to be a UI designer. Responsibilities included product localization, design app and telematics UI. Learning from doing. It makes my determination more strong to be a UI designer.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Marcom / UI Designer Created Visual Identity & Busines Websites

PaXcomn Corp.

Company Profile & Product Power Point

2015/04 - 2017/08

Designed Mobile App UI Informatics & Telematics UI

Manage & Support Tearm Member

Marketing/

Web Designer 友創資訊

2014/08 - 2015/03

Photography

Web Design & Update **Customer Service** 

Art Designer Magatone Corp.

Photography Visual Identity

2008/06 - 2013/07

Graphic Design (Poster, Catalog, Flyer)

Support..

Web Design and Update

Customer Relationship Maintenance

#### **CHARACTERISTICS**

lam: Friendly, Open-minded, Honest and Responsible... I Enjoy: Designing and Thinking, Learning New Thinngs ...



# 楊依婷

平面及使用者介面設計師

## 聯絡我

€

0936178048

etim816@gmail.com

https://etim816.github.io/portfolio/

#### 教育

國立台中科技大學 2006 多媒體設計系 學士

技能

使用者介面設計 使用者體驗設計 原型製作 平面設計



軟 體

Adobe Creative Suite
Photoshop. Illustrator. Indesign
Sketch | Flinto | HTML | CSS3
Power Point | Word

#### 個人簡介

我有8年以上的平面設計經驗。在沛思科通這間新創,階段性工作完成後,加入車載團隊的工作,負責產品在地化及設計車載產品介面,使我走向UI設計這條路。相同點都是以設計來解決問題,使人類的生活更美好,而個人視覺設計偏好是主觀的,我傾向於視覺能讓使用者能夠有更好的使用體驗。

# 經歷

Marcom / 介面設計

美商沛思科通

2015/04 - 2017/08

獨立完成企業識別系統及形象網站建立公司簡介及產品簡報範本智慧型後照鏡在地化設計車載機及手機的介面管理及支援組員工作

行銷/網頁設計師

友創資訊

2014/08 - 2015/03

商品攝影及建檔

產品介紹及網站說計及更新

與客戶溝涌及協調

美術設計

陸商電子

2008/06 - 2013/07

商品攝影

識別系統建立及更新平面設計海報.目錄.傳單

支援

網頁視覺設計及更新

顧客關係維護

個人特質

我是: 友善 開放 誠實 負責任的... 我享受: 設計+思考 學習新的事物...